Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. Classified Files (Part 1)
1921-80
Planned Parenthood Federation of America
371a_s2_p1
83 linear feet
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
Materials in this series relate to the administration of PPFA. It consists of records of the board of directors, executive committee, standing and special committees, and the various divisions and departments of the Federation. The records include correspondence, memos, by-laws, procedures, standards, press releases, reports, statistics, reference materials, and minutes. This series is the core record of Federation activities and policy development. This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records.
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
Materials in this series relate to the administration of PPFA. It consists of records of the board of directors, executive committee, standing and special committees, and the various divisions and departments of the Federation. The records include correspondence, memos, by-laws, procedures, standards, press releases, reports, statistics, reference materials, and minutes. This series is the core record of Federation activities and policy development.
The series is roughly arranged as follows: general policies and histories; committees, bylaws, and handbooks; annual meetings; administrative staff; and then departments and related organizations. Major departments and organizations are as follows: Center for Family Planning Program Development (which was called the Alan Guttmacher Institute beginning in 1975); Community Affairs (later known as Youth and Student Affairs); Field Department, which includes material on abortion; Financial Management; Communications (at times known as Education, Information and Education, or Public Affairs Department); Fund Raising/Resources; Medical (includes material on abortion and contraception); Research (includes clinic statistics); Family Planning International Assistance (includes reports on international family planning projects); and International Planned Parenthood Federation.
NOTE: To view the series descriptions and contents lists, click on the series links below. Some files are quite large and may take several minutes to load, depending on your internet connection.
Due to it's large size, the SERIES II container list is divided into two parts: Part 1 and Part 2.
This collection is organized into ten series:
I. Chronological Files
II. Classified Files
Part 1
Part 2
III. Publications
IV. Subject Files
V. Affiliates
Part 1
Part 2
VI. Regions
VII. Minutes
VIII. Foreign
IX. Guttmacher
[SERIES X. Restricted]
PPFA has closed records created January 1, 1985 or later, with the exception of many published materials which are open to research. All records having to do with clinic defense and security are closed. PPFA has closed a small section of files in box 206 for fifty years. Researchers may request access to restricted materials from PPFA.
The Margaret Sanger Papers Microfilm Edition: Smith College Collection Series, edited by Esther Katz, et al., University Publications of America, 1995
Periodic additions to the collection are expected.
PPFA deposited these records in 1988. Various departments have since sent miscellaneous additions.
Best, Winfield; Guttmacher, Alan Frank, 1898-; McCormick, Katherine Dexter, 1876-1967; Rose, D. Kenneth; Sanger, Margaret, 1879-1966; Wattleton, Faye; Alan Guttmacher Institute--History; American Birth Control League--History; Abortion--Law and legislation-United States--History--Sources; Abortion services--History--Sources; Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau (New York, N.Y.)--History; Birth Control Federation of America--History; International Planned Parenthood Federation--History; Planned Parenthood Federation of America--History; Planned Parenthood-World Population (U.S.)--History; Birth control clinics--United States--History--Sources; Birth control--History--20th century--Sources; Birth control--Developing countries--History--20th century--Sources; Contraceptives--Research--History; Hygiene, Sexual--History--20th century; Human reproduction--Political aspects; Population policy--History--20th century; Reproductive health--Statistics; Sex instruction--History; Women--Health and hygiene--United States--20th century; Women's health services--United States--20th century
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
See also the PPFA I Records.
Related material can be found in the Margaret Sanger Papers, Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College, and at the Library of Congess.
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 1)
  - 1.1 Anniversaries and Special Occasions
    - Planned Parenthood Week, September 14-21, 1965 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Planned Parenthood 50th Anniversary
      - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Publicity Results: Newspaper Clippings, Radio, Television, Win Best, 1966-1966 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Text of Addresses, Debates, Remarks, Symposium, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - General, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - "Early Bird," and Miscellaneous Plans from 1965, 1961-1966 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - [Folder with Handouts from PP 50th Anniversary Conference, Oct. 18-19, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Acceptances, International Sponsors
        - A to H, Council, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - I to P, Council, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Q to Z, Council, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Regrets, International Sponsors, Council, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Remarks of Senator Joseph S. Clark before PPWP 50th Anniversary, Plaza Hotel, New York City, 1/23/1964 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - History, What Planned Parenthood Does, John C. Robbins, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - History, Family Planning Landmarks, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Achievements of PPFA (During Presidency of Alan Guttmacher), 1962-1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Historical Interest Miscellany, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - The Fifties and Sixties, History, Knowledge, Perception and Change: Notes on a Fragment of Social History, Jaffe, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - History, Legal Status and Technical Aspects of Birth Control, 1930-1942 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Merger: PPFA-WPEC
    - PPFA National: Merger, PPFA and WPEC, 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - PPWP: History, Proposed PPFA-WPEC Merger, 1961, Board of Directors Minutes, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Name Changes of The Organization
    - PPFA National: New Name Contest for PP-WP, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - PPWP: History, History of the Changes of Names of the Organization, 1936-1967 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - PP History
    - History, Organized Birth Control, 15 Years Growth, 1924-1936 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - PP History from 1921, 1921-1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Symbols; Logos
    - Symbols (Logos), Miscellaneous, 1954-1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - 1.2 PPWP Policy
    - Policies, 1940-1946 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Policy Statements
    - Policies, Unmarried Mothers, Correspondence, 1955-1966 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Policy Statement, Bequests and Deferred Gifts Program, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Statement of Policy Governing PP's Participation in Biomedical Research, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Repository for Policy Statements
    - Policy Statements from 1976 (formerly, "Repository for,"), 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Repository for Policy Statements, 1970-1975 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 25)
      - 1975 (Box 25)
    - Policy, Definition of Policy for the PPFA, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Policy Statements in General from 1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - 1972 (Box 26)
      - 1980, undated (Box 26)
    - Policy, Premarital Examination (Archives: Minutes of Board of Directors Meetings from 1922), 1922-1950 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence
      - 1969-74 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - 1975-80 (Box 26)
    - Policies from 1969
      - 1969-74 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - 1975 (Box 26)
    - Policies from 1964, 1964-68 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Policies, Unmarried Mothers, 1958-67 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1.3 PPWP Bylaws
    - Correspondence from 1968
      - 1968-74 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - 1975-79 (Box 26)
    - Bylaws, general
      - 1980-75 (Box 26, Folder 9-13)
      - 1974-69 (Box 26, Folder 14-19)
      - Procedures, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - American Birth Control League, 1936; Birth Control Federation of America, 1940, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Certificate of the Incorporation Charter
    - Charter, 1935-49 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Assumed Name Certificate, 1978-79 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Certificate of Incorporation and Changes
      - 1922-74 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - 1975-79 (Box 26)
  - 1.3 PPWP Procedures
    - Correspondence and memos, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - 1975-79 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - 1970-74 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - 1.3 PPWP Standards of Affiliation
    - Correspondence
      - Legal (Paul, Eve), 1978-79 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - 1958-74 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - 1975-78 (Box 26)
    - from 1972
      - 1972-74 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - 1975-78 (Box 26)
    - From 1967, 1967-71 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - From 1947-1967 [Missing 1950-1960] (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Memos, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Proposed Revision and Comments
      - August to November 1978 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      - January to July 1978 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - 1.41 PPWP National Board
    - Board of Directors
      - Analysis of Board And Executive Committee, Policy Decisions, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - General Correspondence
        - 1975-1981 (Box 26, Folder 37)
        - 1973-74-1959-60 (Box 26, Folder 38-44)
  - 1.41 Board of Director's Handbook
    - [Unbound pages of Manual from 1969 (?)] (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - [PPFA, Board of Director's Handbook, Mrs. Fifield Workum] 1963 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - [Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc., Board of Director's Handbook, Mr. John A. Behnke] (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Board of Director's Manual for Self Evaluation for the Board of Directors, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Organizational Charts (PPWP), 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Member Lists
    - Board of Directors
      - 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - 1975-80 (Box 27)
      - 1965-72-1957-64 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
      - Mimeo lists
        - 1936-1954 (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - 1956 (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - 1955 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - PPFA Committee Chairmanships, 1958-1966 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors, List of Black Board, Staff, and Regional Members, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors
      - Board Members by Profession, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - List of Committees of National Board, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Meetings
        - Board Members Ballot, Sheets and Records, Feb. 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 17)
        - Certified Affiliates, Ballot Sheets and Records, Feb. 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 18)
        - Agenda from 1979 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors, Memos, General, 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - 1.41 Board of Directors Minutes
    - 1979 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - General, Memos, etc.
      - 1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - 1975-76 (Box 27)
      - 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Mailing to PPFA Membership, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - 1980-75 (Box 27, Folder 26-30)
    - 1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Documentary Volume for Board of Directors, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Orientation for Board Members, 1965-69 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Performance Objectives for PPFA Board of Directors and President, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - President and Board Evaluation Form, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, Public Affairs Plans for 1978, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Reports
    - Board of Directors
      - Abortion Loan Fund: Report and Proposal, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Chairman's Report, Marshall, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Future Direction for Expansion Medically, Related Family Planning Services, 1976? (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Report on the Federation, Robbins, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Report on Reorganization, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Reports to the Board of Directors
        - 1967-74 (Box 28, Folder 12)
        - 1975-76 (Box 28)
  - Resolutions
    - Board of Directors
      - 1971-74 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - 1975-80 (Box 28)
      - 1946-1970 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer
    - Board of Directors
      - Beach, George R., 1970-73 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - McIntyre, Henry L., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Robbins, John C., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Legal Responsibility, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - PPFA Management Letter, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Treasurer's Reports
    - 1972-74 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - 1975-77 (Box 28)
    - Mary Tams-Beach, 1973-74 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - George R. Beach, 1951-72 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Robbins, John, 1967-1970 (Box 28, Folder 23-24)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1968 (Cincinnati)
    - Correspondence, May 1-4, 1968, 1967-68 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - General Correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - General, Mimeos, May 1-4, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1967 (Denver)
    - General Correspondence, May 4, 6, 7, 1967, 1965-67 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Affiliation Committee, May 4, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Banquet, May 4, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Board of Director's Luncheon, May 6, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Expansion & Policy Committee, May 3, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Fund Raising Committee, May 5, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Press Releases, May 4-5-6, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Professional Staff, May 5, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Symposium: Pop. & Livability in the United States, May 5, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - General, Mimeos, etc., May 4-5-6, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1966 (Washington, D.C.)
    - America's Tomorrow, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Banquet Correspondence, May 5, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Business Correspondence, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Domestic Programs, May 5, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Foreign Aid, May 5, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - General Correspondence, May 5-7, 1966, 1965-66 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Hospital Services, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Lists, May 5-6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence & Information Forms, May 5-6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Poverty Programs, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Public Health, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Professional Consensus, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Religious Consensus, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Research Panel, May 5, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Response to the Public, May 6, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Speeches, May 5-7, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Alan F. Guttmacher, 1966 Meeting (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Press Releases, May 5-7, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Mid-Atlantic Workshop, May 5, 1966, 1965-66 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - General, Mimeos, etc., May 5-7, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1965 (Milwaukee, WI)
    - General Correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Affiliates Meeting, May 6 1965 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Affiliates Staff Meeting, May 7, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Banquet: Ed Morgan, May 6th 1965 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Nationwide Campaign, Materials Committee Meeting, May 5, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Regional & Review Committee Meetings, May 5 1965 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Population & Poverty Panel, May 7 1965, 1964-65 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, May 1965 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Dr. John Rock, Speaker, Board Meeting, May 8, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - General, Mimeos, etc., May 1965 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1964-1961
    - Correspondence, Pittsburgh, PA, April 1961, 1960-61 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - General, Pittsburgh, PA, April 1961, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1960 (Des Moines, IA)
    - Correspondence, April 1960, 1959-60 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - General, April 1960 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - May 5-7, 1959, 1958-59 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Bids, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1963-70 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1980
    - Committee & Task Force Meetings, Memos, Washington, D.C., 1977-80 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1974 (Washington, D.C.)
    - Guttmacher Memorial Funds, 5/31-6/1/74, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - National Medical Committee Meeting, May 29, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Plan for 1975, May 31-June 1, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Memos, Mimeos, General, May 31- June 1, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meeting, 1973 (Boston, MA)
    - Expansion & Policy, May 21, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Future Trends in Abortion, May 21, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Mimeos, General, May 20-23, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meeting, 1972
    - General, Detroit, MI, 5/31/1972-6/3/1972 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1971 (Wilmington, DE)
    - Affiliation Committee, May 14, 1971, 1970-71 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - By-Laws Committee, May 14, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - General Correspondence, 5/12-5/15, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Regional Director's Report, May 12, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Regional Representative's Report, May 13-15, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Mimeos, Programs, 5/12/1971-5/15/1971 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Workshops, May 13, 1971; May 12, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1970 (Savannah, GA)
    - Affiliation Committee, May 8, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Affiliate, National Expansion of Services, May 8, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Banquet, May 8, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, May 9, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - By-Laws Committee, May 7, 1970 (EMPTY) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Expansion & Policy Committee, May 7, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, May 9, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Expenses and Reimbursements, 5/6-5/9/1970 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Family Life Education Workshop, May 7, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 5/6-5/9/70, 1969-70 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - I & E Advisory Committee, May 7, 1970, 1970-72 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Opening Dinner, 5/6/70, Planned Parenthood: The Sign of the Times, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Population Symposium, May 7, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Problem Aspects in the Delivery of Family Planning Services, 5/7/1970 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - S.E. Region Council, Business Meeting, May 6, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Southeast Regional Council Meetings, May 6, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - General, Mimeos, Programs, 5/6/70-5/9/1970 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors, Out-of-Town Meetings, 1969 (Phoenix, AZ)
    - Affiliation Committee, May 1, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Banquet Correspondence, May 1, 1969, 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Challenge for the Future: Abortion, Medical Services, May 1, 1969, 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Expansion & Policy Committee, May 2, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence, 4/30-5/3/69, 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Issues, Images & Interaction: Community Communication, May 2, 1969, 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - New Supporting Services, Planned Parenthood's Role, May 1, 1969, 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Report & Handbook, 4/30-5/3, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Workshops, Regional, May 2, 1969, 1968-69 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - General, Mimeos, etc., 4/30-5/3, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - 1.41 Executive Committee
    - Biographical Material, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - General Correspondence
      - 1970-74 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - 1975-78 (Box 30)
  - Memos, General
    - Executive Committee, Mimeos from 1970
      - 1970-74 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - 1975-79 (Box 30)
  - Member Lists
    - Executive Committee
      - 1957-74 (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - 1975 (Box 30)
  - Report to Executive Committee Meetings
    - Agenda, 1979-80 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - General correspondence
      - 1957-62 (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - 1963-69 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - 1981 Plan and Budget, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - 1980 Program Evaluation and Planning Survey, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - 1.41 Executive Committee Minutes
    - 1979-75 (Box 30, Folder 37-41)
    - 1974-73 (Box 30, Folder 42-43)
    - Meeting, July 17-19, 1980, Budget Decision Process, 1981 Plan & Budget, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Report to Executive Committee, 1968-73 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Resolutions, 1975-78 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Study of the Regions, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Work Paper for Considering Economic Impact of Moving Headquarters, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - 1.42 PPWP Standing Committees
    - 1.42 Affiliation
      - Correspondence
        - 1975-78 (Box 30, Folder 49)
        - 1970-1974 (Box 30, Folder 50-53)
        - 1965-1969 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
      - Evaluation of Services by National & Regional Staff, 2/29/78, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Forms: Applications, Checklists, etc., 1972-74 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Member Lists
        - 1966-74 (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - 1975-78 (Box 31)
      - Memos
        - 1977-78 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Minutes, Affiliation Committee
        - 1973-74 (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - 1975-79 (Box 31)
      - Recommendations to the PPWP Board of Directors, 1970-72 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Regional Affiliation Committees, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Affiliation Committee Subcommittees
      - Subcommittee for Dues Review, 1973-74 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Subcommittee for Planning, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Patient Care, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on State-Wide & Multi-Unit Affiliates, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Standard Operating Procedures Subcommittee, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Standards of Affiliation, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Study: State-Wide and/or Multi Unit Affiliates, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - Standard Operation Procedures, 1974-75 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Affiliates Committee
      - Correspondence, 1965-1961 (Box 31, Folder 20-23)
    - Affiliates Committee, Minutes, General
      - Mimeos and General, 1957-1969 (Box 31, Folder 24-25)
    - Affiliates Relations Committee
      - Meetings, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Affiliates Review, Mimeos, General
      - Mimeos to Affiliates, 1960-63 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Affiliates Review Committee
      - Correspondence
        - 1962-65 (Box 31, Folder 28)
        - Affiliates Review Expansion Committee, Correspondence from December 1962, 1962-1965 (Box 31, Folder 29)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - Meetings, 1963-65 (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Affiliate Development and Evaluation
      - Correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - Instructions for Reporting Form, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - Member Lists, 1979-80 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - Minutes, 1979-81 (Box 31, Folder 36)
      - Minutes, Summary from May 1979, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 37)
      - Think Tank, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - Think Tank, The San Antonio Paper, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Budget and Finance Committee
      - 1973-74 (Box 31, Folder 40)
      - 1975-78 (Box 31)
      - 1972-74 (Box 31, Folder 41)
      - 1975-77 (Box 31)